A man can be pushed too far.
End of Loyalty is a crime, action film directed by Hiroshi Katagiri.
When the head of a notorious crime family is murdered, his son Grant is hell bent on payback and the only person that can stop him
from tearing the city apart and destroying himself in the process is his best friend and federal agent, Ray Rose.
Ray, played by Braxton Angle.
Grant, played by Justice Joslin.
Vincent, played by Simon Phillips.
Jada, played by Tenley Kellogg.
Yukio, played by Sho Ikushima.
Pops, played by Michael Paré.
Garudan (transl.
Brahminy kite) is a 2024 Indian Tamil-language neo-noir
action drama film written and directed by R.
Durai Senthilkumar and jointly produced by Vetrimaaran and K.
Kumar under Grass Root Film Company and Lark Studios.
The film stars Soori, M.
Sasikumar and Unni Mukundan in the leading roles, alongside Roshini
Haripriyan, Sshivada, Revathi Sharma, Samuthirakani, Vadivukkarasi, R.
Udayakumar and Mime Gopi in supporting roles.
It follows Sokkan, a trusted confidante of two childhood friends Aadhi and Karuna,
whose loyalty is changed by a dynamic between betrayal and survival.
The film was officially announced untitled in September 2023, and is Soori's
second film as the story's lead actor, after Viduthalai Part 1.
Principal photography commenced the same month and wrapped in January 2024.
The title Garudan was announced later that month.
The film's music was composed by Yuvan Shankar Raja, while the
cinematography and editing were handled by Arthur A.
Wilson and Pradeep E.
Garudan was released worldwide on 31 May 2024 to positive reviews
from critics and became commercially successful.
It was remade in Telugu as Bhairavam.
The film explores themes of best friend, crime family,
retribution, family rival, violence.